- Can you pass the Parmesan cheese?
- Sure.
(Leonard:)- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to get the hair out of my eyes.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you are one day late
for your haircut.
(Sheldon:)Thank you
for captioning my nightmare.
- Lookie here, I got my travel orders.
- Hmm.
"Payload Specialist Howard Wolowitz
is requested to report...
(Raj:)...to the NASA Johnson Space Center,
Houston, Texas...
(Raj:)...for astronaut training
Monday 8 a.m."
(Howard:)Yeah, but it's from NASA,
so it's 0800.
But it says 8 a.m.
- You read it as 0800.
- It doesn't have an O in front of it.
It does have an O in front of it.
(Howard:)Oh, my God, I'm an astronaut,
and you're dying ofjealousy.
So, what kind of things are they?...
Will you stop that?